http://www.saem.org/lowerfootermenu/privacy

RAMS Committees
Medical Student Ambassadors (MSAs)
RAMS Webinars
Finding a Home Away From Home: Challenges of the Match Faced by URM Applicants and Those Without an Affiliate EM Program
RAMS: The Inside Scoop on Academic Jobs
RAMS: Matching Into EM, How We Got Here and Where Are We Going
Regional Meetings
AACEM Chair Development Program (CDP)
AAAEM Certificate in Academic Emergency Medicine Administration
Advanced Research Methodology Evaluation and Design (ARMED)
John Marx Leadership
Marcus L. Martin Leadership in Diversity and Inclusion Award
Research Tools
Advanced Research Methodology Evaluation and Design (ARMED)
SAEM Grants Guide
Why Do I Want a Grant?
Why Do I Want a Grant?
Help Develop a New Pharma/Device
What Grants are Appropriate?
What Grants are Appropriate?
Overview of Typical Career Pathway
Fellowships (F Series) and Training (T Series)
How Do I Write a Grant?
Sample Grants
SAEM & SAEMF Grants
National Institutes of Health (NIH)
National Institutes of Health (NIH)
View All
Advising Applicants for the 2020-2021 ERAS Application Cycle
Medical Student Rotations in Wilderness Medicine
Resident and Fellowship Opportunities in Wilderness Medicine
CME Courses
Fellowship Opportunities
Research and Scholarship Opportunities in Wilderness Medicine
Wilderness Medicine in Emergency Medicine Physician Organizations
Wilderness Medicine Conferences and Events
FAQs
SAEM Webinars
SAEM Webinars
The New Frontier: DEI Positions in Academic Emergency Medicine
Climate Change and Health Interest Group and Wilderness Medicine Interest Group Webinar Series
Climate Change and Health Interest Group and Wilderness Medicine Interest Group Webinar Series
Environmentally-Responsible Health Care
Climate and Health Education
The Climate Crisis, COVID-19, and Emergency Medicine: Parallels, Intersections, and a Health Recovery
The Power of Nutrition Webinar
PEM IG Virtual Presentation of Top Abstracts from SAEM20
Virtual Mentoring Hour: Teaching Anti-Racism Through Simulation
ADIEM Webinar Series: How to Be a Successful EM Applicant
SAEM Simulation Academy Virtual Mentoring/Faculty Development Hour
Virtual World Health Organization Basic Emergency Care Training of Trainers Course for Health Care Providers
ADIEM Town Hall: Dual Identity: How awareness of racial bias in medicine informs our role as BIPOC physicians
SAEM National Grand Round: COVID-19 Vaccine Distribution and What it Means for the Emergency Department
RAMS Committees
Medical Student Ambassadors (MSAs)
RAMS Webinars
Finding a Home Away From Home: Challenges of the Match Faced by URM Applicants and Those Without an Affiliate EM Program
RAMS: The Inside Scoop on Academic Jobs
RAMS: Matching Into EM, How We Got Here and Where Are We Going
Regional Meetings
AACEM Chair Development Program (CDP)
AAAEM Certificate in Academic Emergency Medicine Administration
Advanced Research Methodology Evaluation and Design (ARMED)
John Marx Leadership
Marcus L. Martin Leadership in Diversity and Inclusion Award
Research Tools
Advanced Research Methodology Evaluation and Design (ARMED)
SAEM Grants Guide
Why Do I Want a Grant?
What Grants are Appropriate?
How Do I Write a Grant?
Sample Grants
SAEM & SAEMF Grants
National Institutes of Health (NIH)
View All
Advising Applicants for the 2020-2021 ERAS Application Cycle
Medical Student Rotations in Wilderness Medicine
Resident and Fellowship Opportunities in Wilderness Medicine
CME Courses
Fellowship Opportunities
Research and Scholarship Opportunities in Wilderness Medicine
Wilderness Medicine in Emergency Medicine Physician Organizations
Wilderness Medicine Conferences and Events
FAQs
SAEM Webinars
The New Frontier: DEI Positions in Academic Emergency Medicine
Climate Change and Health Interest Group and Wilderness Medicine Interest Group Webinar Series
PEM IG Virtual Presentation of Top Abstracts from SAEM20
Virtual Mentoring Hour: Teaching Anti-Racism Through Simulation
ADIEM Webinar Series: How to Be a Successful EM Applicant
SAEM Simulation Academy Virtual Mentoring/Faculty Development Hour
Virtual World Health Organization Basic Emergency Care Training of Trainers Course for Health Care Providers
ADIEM Town Hall: Dual Identity: How awareness of racial bias in medicine informs our role as BIPOC physicians
SAEM National Grand Round: COVID-19 Vaccine Distribution and What it Means for the Emergency Department
RESIZE
Privacy StatementSociety for Academic Emergency Medicine is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Society for Academic Emergency Medicine Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Society for Academic Emergency Medicine website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Collection of Your Personal InformationSociety for Academic Emergency Medicine uses cookies (small text files placed on your device) and similar technologies to collect data. Cookies allow us, among other things, to share your preferences and settings; provide interest-based advertising, and analyze how our services are performing. Our services may include web beacons and cookies from third-party service providers. Data collected may include personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number and anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. You have a variety of tools to control cookies, web beacons and similar technologies, including browser controls to block and delete cookies and controls from third-party analytics service providers to opt out of data collection.There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Society for Academic Emergency Medicine. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Society for Academic Emergency Medicine for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Society for Academic Emergency Medicine Web site.Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Society for Academic Emergency Medicine public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Society for Academic Emergency Medicine does not read any of your private online communications.Society for Academic Emergency Medicine encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Society for Academic Emergency Medicine so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Society for Academic Emergency Medicine is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Society for Academic Emergency Medicine and Society for Academic Emergency Medicine family of Web sites.Use of Your Personal InformationSociety for Academic Emergency Medicine collects and uses your personal information to operate the Society for Academic Emergency Medicine Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Society for Academic Emergency Medicine also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Society for Academic Emergency Medicine and its affiliates. Society for Academic Emergency Medicine may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.In addition, Society for Academic Emergency Medicine may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Society for Academic Emergency Medicine, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.Society for Academic Emergency Medicine does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.Society for Academic Emergency Medicine keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Society for Academic Emergency Medicine, in order to determine what Society for Academic Emergency Medicine services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Society for Academic Emergency Medicine to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.Society for Academic Emergency Medicine Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Society for Academic Emergency Medicine or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Society for Academic Emergency Medicine; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Society for Academic Emergency Medicine, or the public.Security of Your Personal InformationSociety for Academic Emergency Medicine secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Society for Academic Emergency Medicine secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.Changes to This StatementSociety for Academic Emergency Medicine will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Society for Academic Emergency Medicine encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Society for Academic Emergency Medicine is protecting your information.Contact InformationSociety for Academic Emergency Medicine welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Society for Academic Emergency Medicine has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Society for Academic Emergency Medicine at saem@saem.org. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
